MELINIA SUCI RAMADHANI

+6287824317618 | meliniasr14@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/meliniasuciramadhani/ | https://websiteportfolio-meliniasr.github.io

Bogor, Indonesia.

I am graduated from the Informatics Engineering Department taking the Software Engineering study program at Ibnu Khaldun University, Bogor. I have experience building a website project using the PHP Framework (Codelgniter) programming language, working on college internship projects and college final projects. With the soft skills I have, I am able to adapt, communicate, work individually and in teams and apply new technology.

Education

Universitas Ibn Khaldun Bogor ⊙ - Tanah Sereal, Bogor.

Sep 2018 - Nov 2023

Bachelor Degree in Informatics Engineering, 3.56/4.00

- · Join an organization while studying.
- Attend seminars, workshops and conferences held on campus.
- · Practical assistant in the course "Basics of Computer Programming".
- · Take an internship program as a course.
- Participated in the Certified Independent Study and Internship Program (MSIB) activities, namely Bangkit Academy 2022.

Work Experience

Kelurahan Pakansari - Cibinong, Bogor.

May 2021 - Jul 2021

Internship - Web Developer

- Serving the community regarding population administration.
- · Collected and process population administration data using Microsoft Word and Microsoft Excel.
- Recorded Blank Data and Register Data around 100+ data such as: Government Register Data, PKM Register Data, Letter Register Data, and X Bank Register Data.
- Completed the final internship assignment, namely Creating a Website-Based Archives System for Pakansari Village, 100% offline.
- https://github.com/meliniasr/kelurahanpakansari
- https://bit.ly/Internship-Project-Documents

Organizational Experience

Asisten Kajian Islam (ASKI) - Tanah Sareal, Bogor.

Oct 2018 - Dec 2023

Member of Syiar Division

- Attended the inauguration of new members at the "DAURAH ASKI AKBAR" event on 13-14 October 2018.
- During your time as an ASKI member, you participated in every event and served on committees in the Publication & Documentation Division, such as creating designs for brochures, posters, certificates, banners, x-banners, stickers, pins and ID cards.

Himpunan Teknik Informatika (HIMATEKINFO) - Tanah Sereal, Bogor.

Mar 2019 - Nov 2021

Member and Secretary of the Intellectual and Spiritual Division (INROH)

- Attended the inauguration period for new members at the "TADABUR ALAM XVI HIMATEKINFO" event on March 23-24 2019.
- Attended the committee at the "GEBYAR IT" event, served in the Events Division on October 12 2019.
- Attended the inauguration of the division at the "XIV BIG MUSYAWARAH" event on December 12 2020, appointed as Secretary of the Intellectual & Spiritual Division (INROH). Starting to be active in December 2020 November 2021.
- The Secretary is responsible for setting the agenda together with the head of the INROH Division for the implementation of "Ngaji Yasin" every Friday night online in the 2020-2021 term of office.
- The secretary is tasked with recording and storing data required by the INROH Division.
- Attended the volunteer activity "NATIONAL STUDENT VACCINATION MOVEMENT" on September 22 2021, serving as data entry.

Other Skills, Achievements & Experience

- Certification ⊚: Bangkit Academy 2022 : Cloud Computing
- Hardskill: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP Framework: Codelgniter 3/4, MySQL, and GitHub.
- **Softskill** ⊙: Adaptation, Communication, Working individually and in teams, Applying new technology, Indonesian (Native) and English (TOEFL Score: 463 / B1).
- Volunteer Experience ②: Bawaslu RI: Pengawas Tempat Pemungutan Suara (PTPS) 2024, and Himpunan Teknik Informatika (HIMATEKINFO): NATIONAL STUDENT VACCINATION MOVEMENT on September 22 2021 at STKIP Muhammadiyah Bogor, tasked with entering data on Covid-19 vaccination recipients.